“创始吸血鬼”前情提要
ELlJAH: Previously on The Originals...
这座城市曾经是我的家
我要夺回来
This town was my home once.
I want it back.
我们的社区正遭受攻击
Our community is under attack.
拥有强大力量的复活巫师？
是收获祭
Resurrected witches with vast power?
It's the Harvest.
四个女孩照理应该死而复活
Four girls were meant to die
and be reborn.
有人劫走了那力量
Someone jacked that power.
我相信当你深爱着一个人
而那人也同样爱你
I believe that when you love someone
and that person loves you in return,
你会变得格外脆弱
you're uniquely vulnerable.
莎莉丝特，是我害死了她
Celeste, she died because of me.
如果你们能叫我的真名，我会很感激的
叫我莎莉丝特
I'd appreciate it if you'd call me
by my real name. Celeste.
那海莉呢？
What about Hayley?
我的任何背叛都比不上你对她的感情
None of my treachery
will harm this family
给我们家族造成的伤害
as much as your feelings for her.
这把刀包含着
我从吸血鬼身上收获的力量
This blade contains all the power
I harvested from the vampires.
它能做到的是比死亡更可怕的事情
It will do things worse than death.
你准备好最后的献祭了吗？
And are you ready
for the final offering?
救命
Someone help me.
感谢各位前来
这对我来说意义重大
FATHER KlERAN: Thank you all for coming.
It means more than I can tell you.
今天大家齐聚一堂
We gather today
for the first public service
参加教堂重建后第一次布道
of our newly reopened church.
圣安妮终于能再次成为
我们社区的精神寄托
St. Anne's can finally once again
be the heart of our community,
将我们大家聚集在一起
where we can congregate
as a people united.
此时此刻
Here, this hour,
我们齐聚于此赞美上帝
并致上我们的感谢
we come together
to praise God and give thanks.
教堂之前发生的事件是一场悲剧
The events that took place
at our church were tragic.
- 有什么问题吗？
- 没有
-Problem?
-No.
那就专心一点
要让人家觉得我们是虔诚的教区居民
Then pay attention. We're meant
to seem like devoted parishioners.
正因为我们心中仍怀希望
FATHER KlERAN:...and it is that hope
in our hearts,
也因为许多善心人士的慷慨相助
and with the help
of many benefactors,
我们今天才能再次坐在这里
that allows us to be here today.
因此我们以全新的灵魂聚集于此
更加坚强
So, we gather
with renewed spirit made stronger,
致力于爱与和平的理想
committed to the ideals
of peace and love.
- 阿门
-Amen.
-ALL: Amen.
每座坟墓都有人精心打理
Each tomb is well cared for.
人们以爱来悼念自己已故的先人…
Families honor their dead
with displays of affection...
有人吗？
Is someone there?
这座坟墓属于德弗罗家族
这个家族向来因与巫术的紧密联系
...belongs to the Deveraux family,
known throughout the Quarter
闻名于法语区
for their strong connection
to witchcraft.
拜托救救我
(SOBBlNG) Please help me.
仔细看看这里，这些新砌的砖块
And if you look close,
these fresh bricks
说明这个家族最近有人去世了
tell us someone in the family
has recently fallen.
- 那是什么声音？
- 放我出去！
-What is that?
-Let me out.
你好，莫妮克
Hello, Monique.
欢迎回到人间
Welcome back
to the land of the living.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：新月之城
怎么了？发生什么事了？
What is it?
What's going on?
奇迹发生了
It's a miracle.
莫妮克？
Monique?
你活过来了
You're alive? Oh!
主演：约瑟夫摩根
今早的布道真不错，神父
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
KLAUS: Lovely sermon this morning, Father.
非常鼓舞人心
主演：克莱儿荷特
Quite inspirational.
我没想到你会来参加
主演：克莱儿荷特
FATHER KlERAN: I wasn't
expecting you to join us.
我们来是想听听
We were hoping for some word
from your human sources
你对最近的海地入侵有没有什么线索
主演：菲比托金
on the recent Haitian invasion.
我的人已经尽力打听了
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
My guys have their ears
to the ground.
但没有人听到任何
And no one has seen or heard
关于你们说的那个人的消息
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
any sign of whatever his name is.
他叫图德巫父
He's called Papa Tunde.
如今，他身上聚集着所有
主演：莉雅派普斯
And right now,
he's wandering the Quarter
我埋在花园的吸血鬼的力量
with the power he absorbed
正在这附近四处游荡
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
from every soul
I had buried in the garden.
所以你或许该让你的人
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
So, you might want to put your ear
再更加努力一点
a little closer to the ground.
或者我也可以选择逃离这场
Or I could steer clear
of whatever war is brewing
你们之间一触即发的战争
在我还没陷入…
between your kind and his
before I find myself--
恭喜你
I wanted to congratulate you
教堂又重新对大家开放了
on getting the church up
and running.
看得出你现在不方便说话
很高兴见到你，马赛尔
I can see this is a bad time.
Nice to see you, Marcel.
卡蜜
MARCEL: Cami.
别看着我
我已试着让她离开了
Well, don't look at me.
I tried to send her away.
迪亚哥，有什么消息吗？
Yes, Diego,
what do you have for me?
- 我们收到一样特别的东西
- 你能说清楚点吗？
-Uh, we got a special delivery.
- Would you care to elaborate?
不知这代表我们的女巫问题解决了
还是才刚刚开始
DlEGO: Either our witch problems are
over or they're just getting started.
- 马赛尔
- 再见，神父
-Marcel.
-Father.
制片：兰斯安德森
上帝与你同在
God be with you.
谢谢，上帝与你同在
Thank you.
God be with you.
谢谢，上帝与你同在
Thank you.
God be with you.
我可不这么想，但还是感谢你的祝福
Oh, I doubt that
but I do appreciate the thought.
贝丝蒂娜
Bastiana.
当你在地狱见到你侄子西恩时
替我向他问好
Give your nephew Sean my regards
when you see him in hell.
制片：邦妮怀斯
需要什么道具吗，哥哥？
放大镜，还是烟斗？
Can I get you anything, brother?
A magnifying glass, a pipe perhaps?
不如跟大家说说你的看法如何
尼克劳斯？
You have a theory that you'd like
to share with us, Niklaus?
过去，女巫们要表达威胁时
MARCEL: Back in the day,
the witches wanted to send a threat,
她们会杀一只鸡然后放在你门口
they'd just kill a chicken
and leave it on your doorstep.
那这还真是只不吉利的大公鸡啊
你说是吗？
It's rather a large and
ominous chicken, wouldn't you say?
图德巫父轻易制服了蕾贝卡
Papa Tunde defeated Rebekah
with ease,
还差点也解决了我们俩
almost got the two of us as well.
如果他真是跟女巫们一边的
If he was supposed to be
their prize fighter,
为什么她们要杀死他
why leave him for dead
还放在我们前院？
编剧：麦克纳度奇，茱莉普烈克
in our front yard?
看起来你们精神都不错啊
编剧：麦克纳度奇，茱莉普烈克
Well, don't you all look cheery.
听听这个
Listen to this.
今天莎宾在带领游客参观墓地时
A girl literally exploded
from a grave today
一个女孩从坟墓里爬了出来
as Sabine was giving her tour
of the City of the Dead.
- 那女孩是莫妮克德弗罗
- 你说什么？
-lt was Monique Deveraux.
-What?
游客们还以为是安排的表演
The tourists thought
it was part of the show,
但女巫们都认为这是奇迹
导演：克里斯葛瑞斯莫
but the witches are celebrating like
正在大肆庆祝呢
导演：克里斯葛瑞斯莫
it's some kind of bloody miracle.
谁说不是呢？
她们本以为没希望了
Maybe it is.
They think that all hope is lost
但如今一个收获祭女孩突然复活了
but now suddenly a Harvest girl
is resurrected.
或许我们也可以这样救回黛维娜
This is how
we're gonna get Davina back.
杀死取代她位置的女巫
Kill the witch who took her place.
我或许知道那个人是谁
莎莉丝特
I have a theory about who
one of them could be. Celeste.
一定是她
黛维娜之前就试着告诉我们
I mean, it's got to be.
Davina was trying to tell us.
她画了许多莎莉丝特的画像
She was drawing pictures of Celeste.
她是在警告我们邪恶即将来临
She was warning us
that a great evil was coming.
先是图德巫父回来找我们算旧帐
First, Papa Tunde returns
to settle old scores.
现在你那被杀的旧情人也回来了
Now your murdered lover is back.
这不是单纯的女巫攻击吸血鬼事件
This isn't witches attacking vampires.
她们是在向我们宣战
They're declaring war on us.
现在喝酒不算早吧？
It's not too early for Scotch, is it?
毕竟我们要应付一堆女巫的
鬼把戏和阴谋诡计
With all the witches' shenanigans
and subterfuge afoot.
如果你待会要开车的话
这确实太早了
It is entirely too early
if one intends to drive, yes.
是吗？但我可没打算出去
Funny. I don't have any plans
to go anywhere.
她留在这里不安全
She's not safe here.
你得将海莉带到种植园去
You have to take Hayley
to the plantation house
直到这一切结束
until this is over.
你是在担心海莉
还是担心你信不过我？
Are you worried about Hayley
or whether or not you can trust me?
正是因为信任你
我才会请求你做这件事
It's precisely because I trust you
that I'm asking you to do this.
我有个想法
Here's a novel idea.
何不让海莉自己决定呢？
Why don't you let Hayley
decide for herself?
为什么要由你决定她的命运？
Why are you dictating her fate?
你知道的
You know why.
那或许你该亲自带她去
Then perhaps
you should take her yourself.
如果这样做，我就真成了
Well, then that would make me
the very hypocrite
你口中所说的伪君子了
that you've accused me of being.
蕾贝卡，我无法克制自己的情感
Rebekah,
I cannot legislate my feelings.
但我的行为则不同
My actions, however...
所以你能好心帮我这个忙吗？
So, would you kindly do this for me?
你知道这位狼妈妈最不喜欢受人指使了
You know the mama wolf loves
to be told what to do.
她不会喜欢的
但为了你我会这么做
She's not gonna like it
but I will do it for you.
只要能停止我们之间这愚蠢的争执
If only to end this silly quarrel
between the two of us.
你这是在干什么？
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
听着，大家都在四处寻找复活的女巫
Listen, everybody's running off,
looking for resurrected witches.
我想我在教堂见到了其中一个
洁妮薇
Meanwhile, I think I saw one
at the church, Genevieve.
- 你说什么？
- 我不确定
-What?
-I can't be sure.
我只是无意中看到了她
I only caught her out
of the corner of my eye.
之后我一直跟克劳斯在一起
Been with Klaus since.
但那个人看起来很像她
But it looked like her.
我们都知道
And you and I both know
她回来是有原因的
that she would have a reason
to wanna be back.
那些多年前的旧帐
A lot of unfinished business,
那些我们不想被别人知道的秘密
a lot of secrets that you and l
don't want getting out.
我现在要带海莉去种植园
I have to take Hayley
to the plantation.
你得找到洁妮薇，结束这一切
You need to find Genevieve
and end this.
就像上次一样
End it like we did the last time.
请给我杯茶
Tea, please.
- 我很忙
- 卡蜜，听我说
-I'm busy.
-Cami, just hear me out.
我去参加你的教堂重开仪式
You know, I came to your reopening
是因为我想试着去弥补
because I wanted to try
and make amends.
然后我看到你大庭广众之下
跟克劳斯交谈
And then I see you talking
with Klaus out in the open,
一副谈论法语区公事的样子
Iike it's business as usual
in the Quarter.
确实是公事
It is business as usual.
三百多年来
For the past three centuries,
欧康诺家的人一直在努力维护和平
the O'Connells have always tried
to keep the peace.
别跟我扯家族历史
谎话连篇
Save me the family history.
It's all lies on top of lies.
卡蜜，给我倒杯酒
Cami, pour me a drink.
我有事要跟你说
I have to tell you something.
- 基兰叔叔，你怎么了？
- 我有麻烦了
-Uncle Kieran, what's wrong?
-I'm in trouble.
发生在你哥哥西恩身上的事
要在我身上重演了
What happened to your brother Sean
is about to start happening to me.
什么？
What?
我…
I've...
听着，我被下咒了
Look, I've been hexed.
- 我不知道我还剩多长时间
- 等等，我认识一些人
-And I don't know how long I have.
-Wait. I know some people.
一定有办法，我说不清
解药或…
There has to be some sort of,
I don't know, antidote or...
卡蜜，我要你答应我一件事
Cami, I need you
to promise me one thing
一旦情况恶化
that when it gets bad,
你要离我越远越好
I need you to be
as far away from me as possible.
不，不要
一定会有办法解决的
No. No.
There has to be some sort of way.
当然有
Of course there is.
如果你想救你叔叔的命
你只需要拿着这个
If you wanna save your uncle's life,
all you have to do is take this.
然后刺入克劳斯米卡森的心脏
And make sure it ends up
in Klaus Mikaelson's heart.
我以为要让你来这里
I thought I was gonna have
to drag you
得使用一些暴力手段
to the plantation
kicking and screaming.
是啊，但大家都只是想保护我和孩子
对吧？
Yeah. Well, we all just wanna
protect me and the baby, right?
嘿，我是支持你的，记得吗？
出什么事了？
Hey. I'm on your side, remember?
So what gives?
今晚是满月，蕾贝卡
Tonight's a full moon, Rebekah.
那又怎样？你怀孕了，不能变身
So what? You're preggers.
You can't turn.
对，但我想邀请一些人过来
Yes. But I wanted to invite
a few people over.
我懂了
Of course.
精力充沛的美国狼人
Every red-blooded American werewolf
在今晚都会变成长毛利齿的野兽
will be a bundle of fur
and sharp teeth tonight
而你们被诅咒的新月狼族会变成…
whilst your cursed
Crescent clan will be--
人类，但只能维持几小时
Human, but only for a few hours
再变身只能等下个满月了
and won't be again
until the next full moon.
所以我请小约帮我去河口传个话给伊芙
So, I asked Josh to get a message out
to Eve in the bayou.
小约还没死吗？
Josh isn't dead yet?
不错嘛他
我喜欢听精彩的逃生故事
Well, good on him.
I love a nice survival story.
那是谁啊？
Who the bloody hell is that?
- 啤酒桶在后面对吧？
- 是的
-Kegs out back, right?
-Yup.
好吧
Right.
看来你没打算征得我的同意
It appears you weren't gonna wait
for me
就想办一个啤酒派对
to grant you permission
to throw a kegger.
听着，你们都希望我安全，没问题
Listen, you all want me safe, fine.
我会乖乖听话
做象牙塔中的少女
I'll do as I'm told.
I'll play damsel in the glass tower.
但每个月只有今晚我才能见到家人
But tonight's the one night a month
that I can meet my family.
你可以去告我的状，让我被关禁闭
Now, you could rat me out,
send me to my room
或者帮我办个超赞的派对
or you could help me throw
one hell of a party.
以利亚
找我有何贵干？
Elijah.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
我家人需要一名女巫的帮助
My family needs an ally
among the witches
而你曾经帮助过我们
and you've helped us in the past.
也许我们可以一起
阻止一场不必要的争端
Perhaps together we can avoid
an unnecessary conflict.
如果对象是高尚的以利亚
她们可能愿意商量
They may be willing to make a deal
if it were with the noble Elijah.
但只要牵扯到克劳斯
就没有任何和平可言
But there will never be any peace
as long as it involves Klaus.
这就是你们的目的吗？
希望我弟弟离开这里？
Is that what all this is about?
You want my brother out of town?
我只是告诉你她们的想法
I'm just telling you how they feel.
我的族人很害怕，她们虽然绝望
My people are scared.
They're desperate
却并不傻
but they're not dumb.
你的侄女快出生了
You have a niece on the way.
谁都会开始考虑
It stands to reason
you'd be willing to discuss
如何赶他离开
how to run him out of the city.
一起散个步吧
Let's walk together.
你可以带我去参观一下那些著名景点
You can take me
on one of your famous tours.
你得吃点东西
毕竟你经历了这么多
You should eat after everything
you've been through.
我是死过的人了
I was dead.
但你又活过来了啊
But you're here now.
苏菲阿姨，妈妈怎么了？
Aunt Sophie, what happened to Mom?
你妈妈非常爱你
Your mother loved you so much.
她坚信自己能够用魔法
She had faith
that she could use magic
完成收获祭
并让你复活
to complete the Harvest
and get you back.
最后，她为此牺牲了自己
In the end, she sacrificed herself
for the cause,
为了女巫们，为了你
for the witches, for you.
你也跟她有一样的信念吗？
And do you have her faith?
我失去了信念
I lost my faith.
然后我意识到，如果我不相信
Then I realized that if I didn't believe,
一定会让你失望
I would be letting you down.
我试图找回信念，真的
I tried to get it back.
I tried.
莫妮克德弗罗
MARCEL: Monique Deveraux.
法语区的人都在谈论你
Everyone in the Quarter's
been talking about you.
好极了
Classy.
你杀了她妈妈
现在又来威胁她了？
You kill her mother
and now you've come to threaten her?
我不是来威胁谁的
I'm not here to threaten anyone.
你想干什么，马赛尔？
What do you want, Marcel?
收获祭还牺牲了另外三个女孩
There were three more girls
sacrificed during the Harvest.
我想让她们复活
I wanna bring them back.
你骗谁啊？
你才不在乎那些女孩
Who are you kidding?
You don't care about those girls.
你只是想让黛维娜复活
继续利用她的力量
You just want Davina back
so you can use her power again.
- 我只想让她活过来
- 他说的是实话
-I just want her alive.
-He's telling the truth.
- 你怎么知道？
- 我感觉得到
-How do you know that?
-I can feel it.
他对她很忠诚
他是来帮忙的
He's loyal to her.
He's here to help.
我收到你的简讯了
基兰现在在哪？
I got your message.
Where's Kieran now?
他在阁楼休息，祷告
In the attic resting, praying.
他会发疯然后死掉，是吗？
He's gonna go crazy and die, isn't he?
就跟西恩一样
Just like Sean.
我们却还愚蠢地争吵着
And we'll still be in this stupid fight
因为关于女巫的事
吸血鬼的事
because he lied to me
about the witches and vampires.
和你的事，他骗了我
And you.
卡蜜儿
Camille...
我明白你为什么讨厌我
...I can see why you hate me.
说实话，我干过很多可怕的事
Truth be told,
I have done some dreadful things.
但你叔叔是为了保护你才骗你
But the lies your uncle told
were meant to protect you.
他是个好人
忠实可靠
He is a good man with a loyal heart.
他是你的家人
And he is your family.
至于那些女巫
As for these witches,
她们对基兰下手就足以证明
their attack on Kieran
should be proof enough
她们是敌人
they're the enemy.
因此我们要团结起来
In that, we are united.
克劳斯
Klaus.
这是图德巫父的刀
This is Papa Tunde's blade.
一个女巫给我的
Awitch gave it to me.
说它可以造成无边的痛苦和折磨
哪怕对方是吸血鬼真祖
Said it would cause untold pain
and torment, even to an Original.
她说如果我把它刺进你的心脏
She said if I stuck it
in your heart,
她就会治愈基兰
she would heal Kieran.
而你选择了拒绝她们的提议
And yet you chose to reject their offer.
如果我更像你一点，我会下手的
Maybe if I were more like you,
I could do it.
- 但我不…
- 不是恶魔
-But I'm not--
-A monster.
我可不傻
I'm not stupid.
如果有战争要发生
我希望站在赢的一边
If there's a war going on,
I wanna be on the winning side.
来看看怎么救你叔叔吧，好吗？
Let's see what we can do
about saving your uncle, shall we?
又见面了
Hello, again.
我一直盼望着能快点见到你
I'm looking forward to meeting you soon.
你这是开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
一个吸血鬼想要帮你解除
女巫在你身上下的咒
A vampire is trying to reverse
a witch's hex placed on you
你却觉得这杯子亵渎神明
and it's the cup
you find sacrilegious.
- 你确定这样行得通吗？
- 我也不确定
-Are you sure this is going to work?
-Not remotely.
但如果神父体内有马鞭草
But I can't attempt
to use my compulsion
我就不能使用魅惑
to counter Bastiana's curse
来对付贝丝蒂娜的咒语
if the good father
has vervain in his system.
所以先给他放个血
Thus we bleed him out.
我可没说过事情会很容易
I never said this would be pleasant.
就做你该做的事情吧
Just do what you have to do.
我说到做到，马赛尔
如果你再不回电告诉我情况
So, help me God, Marcel,
if you don't call me back with an update,
我就亲手杀了你
I will kill you myself.
不好意思
I beg your pardon.
我以为客人会更毛茸茸一点
I was expecting someone furrier.
你是其中一个，对吗？
吸血鬼真祖
You're one of them, aren't you?
An Original.
对，你的语气可以稍微尊敬一点
Yes. You might want to say that
with some more respect.
- 我想你是要找海莉吧
- 或者我也可以跟你聊聊
-I suppose you'll be wanting Hayley.
-Or I could just talk to you.
我叫奥利佛
还不知道你叫什么
I'm Oliver.
I didn't catch your name.
蕾贝卡
I'm Rebekah.
海莉，参加派对的人来了
Hayley, the party's here.
你的力量还够找到那些女巫吗？
You got enough power left
to find these witches?
我知道收获祭是个大失败
但我还有能力施定位咒的
I know the Harvest was an epic fail
but I can still do a locator spell.
在那之前
我们得做个交易
Before I do that,
we need to make a deal.
什么交易？
What deal?
如果我背叛了这些女巫
她们会来找我麻烦
If I betray these witches,
they're gonna come looking for me.
如果我被抓住，我就死定了
And if I'm caught, I'm dead.
我说了我会保护你
I said I'd protect you.
如果你真能做到
If you could do that,
一开始你也不会找我帮忙了
you wouldn't need my help
in the first place.
法语区危机四伏
The Quarter isn't safe.
吸血鬼雄踞一方
女巫与之对抗自成一派
Vampires on one side,
witches on the other.
我绝不可能让莫妮克陷入其中
No way am I letting Monique
get in the middle of that.
为了带她离开
我需要钱
In order to get her out,
I'm gonna need money.
成交吗？
Do we have a deal?
找到那些女巫
我会给你想要的一切
Find the witches, I'll give you
anything you could ever need.
来吧，你可以跳得更好的
Well, come on.
You can do better than that.
抱歉，我今晚脑子很乱
Sorry.
I've got a burdened brain tonight.
不行，不行
今晚得抛开所有包袱
No, no, no.
Tonight is not a night for burdens.
好好庆祝一番
It's to celebrate.
尽情享受
It's to enjoy life
这几小时的人类生活
for the few hours
that we get to live it.
我们要拥抱朋友、家人
还要疯狸地跳舞
It's to hug our friends, our family
and to dance our asses off.
我不信你邀请我们来只是为了招待我们
MAN: I seriously doubt
you invited us here to wait on us.
你是海莉，我叫杰克森
You're Hayley.
I'm Jackson.
很高兴又见面了
It's nice to see you again.
你就是那头一直看着我的狼
You're the wolf
who's been watching me.
我必须要盯着你
以及你体内的珍品
I got to keep my eye on you,
precious cargo and all.
没错
得保护这个奇迹般的孩子
Right.
Got to protect the miracle baby.
不，我不是这个意思
我不在乎这个孩子
No. That's not what I meant.
I don't care about the baby.
抱歉，那样说不对
我当然在乎孩子
Sorry. That came out wrong.
I mean, of course I care.
你是拉伯奈家族的一员
孩子就是大事
You're a Labonair.
A baby, it's a big deal.
但我个人对你更有兴趣
But personally,
my interest is in you.
你根本不认识我
You don't even know me.
我们的父母互相认识
Our parents knew each other.
他们是同一阶级的人
但不是同一血脉
They were of the same people
but not the same bloodline.
你知道狼族阶级制度是如何运作的吧？
Now, you know
how pack hierarchy works, right?
每个人都有设定好的角色
我们也不例外
Everybody has their part to play
and we had our part too.
我们的角色是什么？
What part was that?
你应该是我的妻子
You were supposed to be my wife.
接下来的这片区域是城里为数不多
SABlNE: So this next part of town
is one of the few areas
还保留着最初法国建筑的地区之一
where any of the original
French architecture remains.
大部分建筑在18世纪就毁了
Most of the buildings
were destroyed in the 1700s
那时大火第一次吞噬了这座城市
when the city burned
for the first time.
我说这些很无聊吧？
Am I putting you to sleep?
你可能觉得惊讶
As surprising
as you might find this,
并不是每天都有人要你
it's not every day
that someone asks you
背叛自己的兄弟…
莎莉丝特
to betray your own brother, Celeste.
你怎么发现的？
How did you know?
当黛维娜画了你的画像时
As Davina was drawing your likeness,
我就大胆猜测你就在附近
I dared to imagine
that your presence was near.
然后当苏菲发现
And when Sophie discovered
你的遗骸里没有法力
我便怀疑
that there was no magic
in your remains, I wondered...
你是不是有可能诈死
Could you have possibly
cheated death
用法力将你的本体
by using your power
to place your essence
转移到其他人体内？
into the body of another?
如果是这样，那会是谁？
And if so, then who?
然后我回想起可爱的莎宾
And then I recalled the lovely Sabine.
你要一直跟踪我吗，以利亚？
Are you gonna continue
following me, Elijah?
还是你想谈谈？
Or do you wanna talk?
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
老是穿西装的吸血鬼真祖
Original vampire,
always wears a suit?
你看到了我弟弟孩子的幻象
Your visions of my brother's child
促成了你们女巫最后一位长老的死亡
precipitated the death
of the last elder within your coven.
告诉她们你看到了什么
Tell them what you saw.
你要确保收获祭仪式绝不能完成
Ensuring that the Harvest ritual
could not be completed
除非你能掌控它
unless you were to control it.
你真的下了很大的一盘棋
You have been playing
a very long game indeed.
为了什么？
To what end?
以利亚
我失落的爱人
Oh, Elijah... my lost love.
经过这么长时间
After all this time...
你还不明白吗？
Don't you understand?
我因克劳斯而死
I died because of Klaus.
就算是他这样恶意中伤女巫害死了我
Even after all his vindictive lies
about witches led to my death,
你仍站在他那边
只因你“永远在一起”的誓言
you stood by him all because
of your vow, "Always and forever."
你对我做了什么？
What have you done to me?
就是个简单的法术
不用担心
It's a simple enchantment.
You needn't worry.
我不是来杀你的，以利亚
I'm not here to kill you, Elijah.
我要让你知道你的方式是错的
I'm here to teach you
the error of your ways.
“永远在一起”是你一生最大的错误
Always and forever was the greatest
mistake of your life.
喝了它
能治好你的伤
Drink up.
It will heal your wound.
我觉得你受的苦已经差不多了
I think you've suffered enough.
你会战胜
女巫对你所做的一切
You will overcome
what the witches did to you.
你能抵抗她们的魔法带来的黑暗冲动
You will resist
the dark urges of their hex.
- 有用吗？
- 我怎么知道有没有用
-Did it work?
-How do I know if it worked?
我只知道我体内没有马鞭草了
All I know is that the vervain is out
只能任由这个杀人魔摆布
and I'm at the mercy
of this murderous bastard.
你一定觉得这很好笑对吧
卡蜜，你这个小…
I bet you find that really funny,
don't you, Cami, you little--
对不起
我不知道我为什么会说这些
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I said that.
好吧
这就是答案了
Well, I guess that's our answer.
等等
克劳斯，你要去哪？
我们该怎么办？
Wait. Klaus, where are you going?
What are we going to do?
我要去查出是哪个女巫干的
I'm gonna find the witch
who did this.
然后我就要做我最拿手的事
And then I'm gonna do
what I do best.
我比我想像的要弱
I'm weaker than I thought.
你想要交易，苏菲
那你就得遵守诺言
You want the deal, Soph,
you got to hold up your end.
我时间紧迫
I'm on a clock.
好吧
SOPHlE: Okay.
成功了
It's working.
那才一个，我要三个
That's one.
I need all three.
我正在尽我所能
I'm giving you whatever I can pick up.
- 继续努力
- 或者不用了
-Keep trying.
-KLAUS: Or don't.
筹码就在眼前
Who needs a locator spell
我还需要什么定位咒呢？
when I have all the leverage
I need right here?
不，莫妮克
No! Monique!
你居然利用亲我的时候下毒
You've poisoned me with a kiss.
至少你还跟以前一样爱讽刺人
At least you haven't lost
your sense of irony.
我们也许还有时间说点别的
We may have time for more.
但首先我要把你最大的缺点治好
But first, I'm going to cure you
of your greatest flaw.
这种荒谬的对疯子般家人的奉献
This absurd devotion
to your lunatic family.
我也和你一样愤怒
Your anger is with me.
如果你是来报仇的…
Now, if you have come here
seeking revenge--
仇我一定会报
从克劳斯开始
Oh, I'll have my revenge,
starting with Klaus.
他会尝到前所未有的痛苦和折磨
He is gonna know pain and torment
like he's never felt before.
当然，除非你选择要救他
Unless you choose to save him,
of course.
但那就剩下了蕾贝卡
你悲惨的妹妹
But then that leaves Rebekah,
your tragic sister.
她马上就会发现自己深陷窘境
She's about to find herself
in quite the predicament.
你可以救她
You could save her.
但那样海莉就危险了
But then
that leaves Hayley in jeopardy.
- 不，不，不
- 这个可怜的女孩
-No. No, no.
-Ah, this poor girl.
她完全不知道被你所爱
是一件多么危险的事
She has no idea how dangerous it is
to be loved by you.
当然
Oh, well.
你的身体被我的咒语所削弱
你不可能救他们所有人
With your body weakened by my spell,
you won't be able to save them all.
你恢复后的时间只够你选择救一个人
You'll recover
with just enough time to choose one.
会是谁呢？
真是迫不及待想知道呢
Who will it be?
I can't wait to find out.
法语区的女巫们
KLAUS: Witches of the French Quarter,
我身边这位是莫妮克德弗罗
I have with me Monique Deveraux.
刚刚脱离死亡的她
What a shame it would be
如果被我不得不再次杀死，就太可惜了
were I forced to send her back
to the death she's just escaped.
不想让这种事情发生的话
就把女巫贝丝蒂娜给我带来
Should you wish to prevent this,
bring me the witch Bastiana.
你这是在干什么？
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
我在谈判啊
I'm opening negotiations.
你知道我的规矩，我们不伤害孩子
You know my rules.
We do not hurt kids.
省省你那虚伪的道德准则吧
Spare me the hypocrisy
of your moral code.
那也没能阻止你杀死莫妮克的妈妈
It didn't stop you
from killing Monique's mother.
贝丝蒂娜
Bastiana.
我知道你就在附近
I know you're close.
空气中弥漫着女巫的恶臭
The stench of witches hangs in the air.
记住我的话
Mark my words.
我要用你打算
I will end this girl
对付我的这把刀杀死这女孩
with the very blade
you meant for me.
我不会再说第二遍
I'm not saying it again!
我们不杀孩子
We do not kill kids.
在这里，由我决定谁生谁死，马赛勒斯
I decide who lives
and dies here, Marcellus.
接着就交给我吧
I'll take it from here.
- 我知道这很难接受
- 你觉得是吗？
-I know it's a lot to take in.
-You think?
我只是想见见我的家人
I just wanted to meet my family.
我从没想过我会过见我的丈夫
I never imagined
I'd meet my husband
还是什么奇怪的安排婚姻
from some weird-ass
arranged marriage.
我猜你对此一无所知
I guess you don't know about
any of this
因为你身边没有人教导你
because there was never anyone
around to teach you.
新月狼族并不只是随便的一群狼
The Crescents aren't just
any pack of wolves. Okay?
此一血脉可追溯到最开始
The bloodline goes back
to the very beginning.
两个家族，你的和我的
Two families.
Yours and mine.
我想这就让我们变得跟皇室一样了
I guess that makes us kind of like royalty.
这是玩笑，对吧？
This is a joke, right?
如果你是皇室，你的王座在哪呢？
I mean, if you're royalty,
where's the throne?
纽奥良曾经是我们的城市
New Orleans used to be our town.
因为一些明争暗斗，我们失去了一切
And we lost it all because
of some infighting.
在我们之后吸血鬼来了
The vampires came after us.
如果我们的家族团结起来
我们本可以打败他们
And if our families were united,
we could have taken them.
所以我们的父母决定
So, our parents decided
将两个家族合并起来
to bring the two lines
back together.
我们两个就订婚了
And you and I were betrothed.
抱歉，这太荒谬了
I'm sorry.
This is ridiculous.
听着，显然事情并没有像
Look, obviously things
didn't work out
大家想的那样发展
the way anyone thought they would.
我们狼群犯了个巨大的错误
Our pack made a huge misstep
with the vampires
我们拒绝对吸血鬼妥协
马赛尔就叫女巫给我们下了咒
when we refused to back down.
And Marcel had us cursed by a witch.
你是你家族血脉的最后一人了
安德莉亚
You are the last one
of your bloodline, Andrea.
或是海莉，不管你怎么称呼自己
Or Hayley.
Whatever you call yourself.
这些人会跟随你
These people will follow you.
你可以帮助他们
你以及你所代表的
You can help them,
you and what you represent.
那到底是什么呢？
And what is that exactly?
一切还是不同的时候
我们的族人还在抗争的时候
A time when things were different,
when our people fought back.
你历经艰辛找到我们
And after everything
you went through to find us.
你是唯一能打破诅咒的人
You're the one
who's gonna break our curse.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
你的女巫朋友
Your witch friend.
她告诉伊芙她今晚会来
She told Eve
she was coming here tonight
解除我们的咒语
to set us free.
等等，什么女巫朋友？
Wait. What witch friend?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很喜欢你
但我跟别人约定好了
I really do like you
but this is the deal we made.
什么约定？跟谁？
What deal? With whom?
海莉
Hayley.
以利亚，女巫们在谋划着什么
Elijah, something's going on
with the witches.
听我说，你说得没错
莎莉丝特回来了
Listen to me. You were right.
Celeste is back.
尼克劳斯、蕾贝卡
你们的处境都很危险
Niklaus, Rebekah.
You're all in danger.
- 怎么回事？
- 这是个陷阱
-What's going on?
-It's a trap.
- 我没跟任何女巫做过约定
- 什么？
-I didn't make a deal with witches.
-What?
海莉，你得找到蕾贝卡
Hayley, you have to find Rebekah.
在我到之前和她待在一起
And you stay with her
until I get there.
以利亚，这是个咒语
我们被困在屋内了
Elijah, it's a spell.
They're trapping us inside.
你知道怎么做
You know what to do.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
来，透过这个呼吸
Here. Breathe through this.
- 蕾贝卡呢？
- 不知道
-Where's Rebekah?
-I don't know.
她跟其中一个人出去了
She went off with one of them.
以利亚，我朋友还在里面
Elijah, my friend is still in there.
站起来
On your feet.
帮帮我
Help me.
好久不见了，蕾贝卡
It's been such a long time, Rebekah.
我会好好享受这过程的
I'm going to enjoy this.
丢了什么东西吗？
SABlNE: Missing something?
你不会伤害我的
我是唯一活着
You won't hurt me.
I'm the only one alive
能打破海莉家族诅咒的人
who can break the curse
on Hayley's family.
而洁妮薇知道你妹妹在哪
And Genevieve knows
where your sister is.
贝丝蒂娜把克劳斯
藏在一个安全的地方
Bastiana has Klaus
tucked away someplace safe.
顺便说一句，他正在痛苦煎熬
He's suffering horribly,
I might add,
那都是因为你选择去救那只小狼
and all because you chose
to save the little wolf
而不是你的家人
instead of your own blood.
多么可怕的结局
What a horrific ending...
对你那可悲病态的家族来说
...to your pathetic, diseased family.
我想“永远”终究不会是永恒
I guess "always" isn't forever after all.
我得走了，月亮
I have to go. The moon.
听着，杰克森
Listen, Jackson,
我想谢谢你保护我
不只是今晚
I want to thank you
for protecting me, not just tonight.
我从儿时起就一直幻想着
I've been dreaming
about meeting you,
我们的见面
since I was a kid.
我从没想过会变成这样
I never thought it would go like this.
嘿
Hey...
我会一直寻找
直到找到打破诅咒的方法
...I won't stop until I find a way
to break this curse.
我保证
I promise.
快点，快点，快点接啊
Come on. Come on. Come on.
克劳斯，你在哪？
Klaus, where are you?
米卡森先生现在正身体不适
Mr. Mikaelson is currently indisposed.
怎么了？你做了什么？
What happened?
What did you do?
什么都没做
有人替你完成了你的任务
I did nothing.
Someone completed your task for you.
如果你得到了你想要的，那我叔叔…
If you got what you wanted,
then my uncle--
很快就会死去，并且会极其痛苦
Will die soon and in great anguish.
你瞧，亲爱的
你没能遵守我们的协定
You see, dear, you failed
to hold up your end of our bargain.
你叔叔多次与邪恶为友
You chose instead to side with evil
而你也和他一样
as your uncle has done
many times before you.
不过振作点
But take heart.
他的惩罚将会弥补
His punishment will atone
他数次尝试阻止收获祭
for his attempts
to prevent the Harvest.
他的痛苦将会净化他
His suffering will purify him.
你吸取他的教训就会做得更好了，孩子
You'd do well
to heed his lesson, girl.
与我们作对就是与自然秩序作对
To oppose us
is to oppose the natural order.
无论自愿或被迫
By choice or by force,
法语区的女巫们将再次崛起
the witches of the French Quarter
will rise again.
我们到处都找过了
We looked everywhere for him.
把女巫区、墓地都翻遍了
Tore apart the Cauldron,
the City of the Dead.
不管他被抓到哪，一定不在法语区
Wherever they got him,
he ain't in the Quarter.
马赛尔！
ELlJAH: Marcel!
我弟弟在哪？
Where is my brother?
我的人正在外面找他
I got guys out looking for him
right now.
以利亚
Elijah.
克劳斯又冲我发脾气了
Klaus threw one
of his classic temper tantrums,
扭断了我的脖子
试图独自一人与一群女巫较量
snapped my neck, tried to take
on a coven of witches by himself.
结果被制服了
He got dropped.
我不知道他在哪，也不知道怎么找他
I don't know where he is
or how to find him.
她们还抓走了蕾贝卡
They also have Rebekah.
在场的每一人都要帮我找到他们
Every one of you will help me
to find them!
我要把她们都杀光
I'm going to kill them all.
- 快点，我们该走了
- 我不想走
-Come on. We have to go.
-I don't wanna go.
莫妮克，这没得商量
Monique, this isn't a debate.
我刚刚捅了一个真祖
I just stabbed an Original.
他一旦恢复就会杀了我的
He's gonna kill me
as soon as he's recovered.
听着
对于这一切我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry for everything.
我应该在那个愚蠢的收获祭前
把你救出来的
I should have come and got you
before that stupid Harvest.
但你还是可以拥有正常的生活
But you can still have a normal life.
没有这些疯狂荒诞的女巫事
One without all this crazy witch nonsense.
但我就是女巫
But I am a witch.
我不想走
And I don't want to go.
莫妮克？
Monique?
祖先们说你的信念不坚定
The ancestors said
you didn't have enough faith.
我还希望是他们错了
I was hoping they were wrong.
我早该知道的
I should have known better.
- 莫妮克
- 你试图阻止收获祭
-Monique.
-You tried to stop the Harvest.
求你不要这么做
Please don't do this.
现在我们该留下来战斗时，你却想逃走
Now you want to run
when we need to stay and fight.
别这样，求求你，不要，不要
Please. I'm begging you, don't--
Don't--
我们四个人，我们死而后生时
The four of us, when we return,
就有足够的力量除掉城里的吸血鬼
we'll have enough power
to rid the city of vampires
我们会杀死每一个
and we'll kill anyone...
信念不坚定的人
...who doesn't keep the faith.
- 莫妮克，求求你
- 你应该相信的
-Monique, please.
-You should have believed.
住手，求求你
Stop. Please.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）